Finding Aid for the Stanley Kramer Papers LSC.0161
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Films, (Document Boxes)
  - Judgment: The Court Martial of the Tiger of Malaya - General Yamashita
    - Transcripts (Calley vs. U.S. Army).
      - 18. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 2068-2220. (Box 169)
      - 19. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 2069-2131. (Box 169)
      - 20. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 2221-2305. (Box 169)
      - 21. vol. 3, Book 6: pp. 2306-2793. (Box 169)
      - 22. vol. 3, Book 6: pp. 2306-2793. Incomplete. (Box 169)
      - 23. vol. 3, Book 6: pp. 2328-2590. (Box 170)
      - 24. vol. 3, Book 6: pp. 2591-2783. (Box 170)
      - 25. vol. 3, Book 7: pp. 2794-3151. (Box 170)
      - 26. vol. 3, Book 7: pp. 2804-2844. (Box 170)
      - 27. vol. 3, Book 7: pp. 2794-3099. (Box 170)
      - 28. vol. 3, Book 7: pp. 2845-3569. (Box 171)
      - 29. vol. 3, Book 8: pp. 3152-3753. (Box 171)
      - 30. vol. 3, Book 8: pp. 3162-3266. (Box 171)
      - 31. vol. 3, Book 8: pp. 3267-3454. (Box 171)
      - 32. vol. 3, Book 8: pp. 3455-3752. (Box 172)
      - 33. vol. 3, Book 9: pp. 3754-4002. (Box 172)
      - 34. vol. 3, Book 9: pp. 3754-4257. (Box 172)
      - 35. vol. 3, Book 9: pp. 4004-4216. (Box 173)
      - 36. vol. 3, Book 9: pp. 4217-4257. (Box 173)
      - 37. vol. 3, Book 10: pp. 4258-4517. (Box 173)
      - 38. vol. 3, Book 10: pp. 4475-4590. (Box 173)
      - 39. vol. 3, Book 10: pp. 4258-4699. (Box 173)
      - 40. vol. 3, Book 10: pp. 4591-4699. (Box 174)
      - 41. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 4700-5079. (Box 174)
      - 42. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 4700-4776. (Box 174)
      - 43. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 4777-4884. (Box 174)
      - 44. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 4885-4956. (Box 174)
      - 45. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 4857-5042. (Box 174)
      - 46. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 5043-5079 (2). (Box 174)
      - 48. vol. 3, Book 11: pp. 331-1031. Exhibits included. (Box 175)
    - Folders
      - 1. Wolper Prod. (Box 161)
      - 2. Calley (2). (Box 161)
      - 3. Cast Lists. (Box 161)
      - 4. Revisions--General. (Box 161)
  - Member of the Wedding, 1952.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 5)
    - First estimating draft by Edward and Edna Anhalt., May 9, 1952. (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by Edward and Edna Anhalt., May 26, 1952. (Box 296)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 5)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 5)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Julie Harris).
  - The Men, 1950.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 1)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 1)
    - Script. Carl Foreman. (Box 246)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuity. (Box 246)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 7)
    - 10 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 9)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 1)
    - 235 stills, 8" × 1C. (Box 2)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars Award, 1950.
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Marlon Brando). (Box 357)
    - National Rehabilitation Association Plaque, 1950-51. (Box 301)
    - Varsity magazine plaque for The Men, 1950. (Box 123)
  - My Glorious Brothers (not produced).
    - Three drafts, original typescript, heavily annotated throughout by Ned Young and Harold Smith, 150 pages holograph by Ned Young. (Box 103)
    - Script--Adaptation by Howard Fast, March 14, 1958. (Box 296)
    - Script--First draft screenplay, March 1966. (Box 296)
    - Script. Screenplay by Nathan E. Douglas and Harold Jacob Smith. From the novel by Howard Fast. (Box 297)
    - First draft, annotated by Young and Smith, January 14, 1960. (Box 104)
    - First draft, revised, annotated by Young and Smith, April 25, 1960. (Box 104)
    - First draft, further revised, annotated by Young and Smith, 1960. (Box 104)
    - First draft, heavily annotated by Smith, 1960. (Box 104)
    - Second draft, annotated by Young and Smith, July 15, 1960. (Box 105)
    - Second draft, further revised, in orange cover, annotated by Young and Smith, 1960. (Box 105)
    - Third draft, annotated by Young and Smith, January 19, 1961. (Box 105)
    - Third, draft, revised, annotated by Young and Smith, February 2, 1961. (Box 105)
    - 100 original wardrobe sketches, 10 × 13½, by Renie. (Box 352, Box 353, Box 354)
    - My Glorious Brothers--General Correspondence. (Box 254)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and work sheets. (Box 106)
    - 53 original wardrobe sketches by Renie, 10½ × 13½. (Box 107)
    - Sample fabric swatches. (Box 107)
      See also: Boxes 352, 353, 354.
  - My Six Convicts, 1952.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 4)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 4)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 4)
    - My Six Convicts. Script. Final draft by Michael Blankfort., September 10, 1951. (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Script. Michael Blankfort., September 10, 1951. (Box 247)
    - Dialogue Continuity. (Box 247)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph.
    - 29 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 11)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 10)
  - Not as a Stranger, 1955.
    - Final shooting script, including all changes. (Box 9)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Frank Sinatra).
    - Script, (2)., September 2, 1954 (Box 247)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuity. (Box 247)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 9)
    - 230 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 9)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Music and songs). (Box 10)
    - Production files (Negative cost - United Artists). (Box 11)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 9)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 8)
    - 27 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - 34 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 10)
    - 10 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 9)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - 25 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 9)
    - 3 Photographs (Box 375, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma Crude
    - Actors & Agents. (Box 177)
    - Call Sheets. (Box 177)
    - Columbia Pictures Correspondence. (Box 177)
    - Comment, Congrats, Quotes etc. (Box 177)
    - Crank letters. (Box 177)
    - Daily Production Reports. (Box 177)
    - Day out of Days Schedule. (Box 177)
    - Dunaway, Faye (Contract). (Box 177)
    - Editorial. (Box 177)
    - Tape
      - 1. Roll 2A. (Box 192)
      - Film (Television clips) Sent to Film Archive, UCLA, Theatre Arts Department.
      - 2. T. Kratochuil, July 16, 1973. (Box 192)
      - 3. Send a little love my way. (2) (Box 192)
      - 4. Five-minute feature with S. Kramer, Faye Dunaway & G.C. Scott. (Box 192)
      - 5. Chuck Walsh review, August 1, 1973. (Box 192)
      - 6. Five-minute featurettes. (Box 192)
      - 7. Radio interview with S. Kramer--San Francisco. (Box 193)
      - 8. Unmarked. (Box 193)
    - Scripts
      - 1. First draft:, January 11, 1972. (Box 187)
      - 2. First draft:, January 11, 1972. (Box 187)
      - 3. First draft, 152 pp. standard format. (Box 187)
      - 4. Final draft:, with S. Kramer notations., June 1, 1972 (Box 188)
      - 5. Final draft:, with S. Kramer notations., June 1, 1972 (Box 188)
      - 6. Final draft:, with S. Kramer notations., July 31, 1972 (Box 188)
      - 7. Revised script, August 23, 1972. (Box 188)
      - 8. Continuities, combined (Cutting & Dialogue). (Box 188)
      - 9. Incomplete revisions (Production #8246) outtakes. (Box 188)
      - 10. Production script with notations. (Box 189)
      - 11. Personal S. Kramer script. (Box 189)
    - Retyped--one copy for S. Kramer, April 26, 1972. (Box 194)
    - Outtakes from S. Kramer's script. (Box 193)
    - Pages deleted from original script. (Box 194)
    - Slides, (2 trays)
      - 1. Maria Cosindas--Special Photographer., 2 trays, ca. 200 pieces. (Box 189)
      - 2. Productions slides--envelope 23. (Box 189)
    - Marc Norman--Novelization manuscript., 235 leaves, First draft. (Box 193)
    - Audience reactions cards., (approximately 300) (Box 194)
    - Press book., (2 Folders) (Box 194)
    - Cast/crew. (Box 194)
    - Press visiting location. (Box 194)
    - Reviews. (Box 194)
    - Costume designs for Faye Dunaway by Bill Thomas. (9). (Box 357)
    - Costume descriptions & pictures. (Box 194)
    - Oklahoma Crude (record). (Box 193)
    - Production notes, 6 packets.
      missing - not received
    - Photocopied articles on Oklahoma Crude. (Box 194)
    - Contact prints, 1 - 2315 and 2316 - 4390. (Box 355)
    - Production Board Picture Negatives (accordion folder).
    - Oklahoma Crude - cutting & dialogue. (Folder 6)
    - 1. Script--First draft: Screenplay by Marc Norman., January 11, 1972. (Box 297)
  - On the Beach, 1959.
    - First draft screenplay, heavily annotated by Stanley Kramer. (Box 20)
    - First draft screenplay revised. (Box 20)
    - Revised script, (2)., December 8, 1958 (Box 247)
    - Continuity (Box 249)
    - Cutting continuity (4). (Box 249)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuity. (Box 249)
    - Script, December 8, 1958 (Box 249)
    - Revised Script, December 8, 1958 (Box 248)
    - Draft of script from France by John Paxton, original typescript. (Box 20)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 20)
    - Stills, 15 pieces. (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Stills, 11 × 14. (112) in two albums. (Box 305)
    - Music sketches. (Box 340)
    - Model submarine, The Nautilus (damaged). (Box 338)
    - 230 production stills. (Box 21)
    - 230 production stills. (Box 22)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Clearances). (Box 23)
    - Production files (Comments - M.P.P.A.). (Box 24)
    - Production files (Music cue sheets - Publicity). (Box 25)
    - Production files (Riverside International Raceway - Zagon). (Box 26)
      See also: Boxes 305, 306, 307, 338, 340, 357.
    - Limelight award plaques for On the Beach,, and Inherit the Wind., 1960; Two items. (Box 121)
    - Page One Award plaque,, in case., April 1, 1960 (Box 305)
    - Medal, Montevideo, Uruguay, April 1960. (Box 305)
    - Screen Producers Guild nomination for Best Production,, framed., 1959 (Box 305)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Gregory Peck). (Box 357)
    - 16 mm print of the press conference at the Premier Chinese Theatre, December 17, 1959. (Box 305)
    - Framed matchbook from Yacht Club, Australia. (Box 305)
    - Sterling silver cigarette box from crew, Melbourne, Australia. (Box 305)
    - 14 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - 41 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - 42 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 9)
    - Port of Trinidad, Spain, silver plaque for On the Beach, 1960. (Box 122)
    - La Hova Finne Trophy for On the Beach, 1960. (Box 330)
  - Pressure Point, 1962.
    - First draft teleplay by Dr. Robert Lindner, adapted for television by S. Lee Pogostin. Originally titled Destiny's Tot. (Box 47)
    - First draft revised teleplay by S. Lee Pogostin. (Box 47)
    - Final draft revised teleplay by S. Lee Pogostin. (Box 47)
    - First draft - working title. (Box 250)
    - Script, (2)., n. d (Box 250)
    - Dialogue Continuity. (Box 250)
    - Cutting continuity. (Box 250)
    - Final draft:, September 13, 1961. (Box 250)
    - Story notes for screenplay by Hubert Cornfield, July 28, 1961 and August 31, 1962. (Box 47)
    - First draft screenplay by Hubert Cornfield. (Box 47)
    - First draft revised by Hubert Cornfield. (Box 47)
    - First draft screenplay by Stanley Kramer, original typescript, annotated. (Box 47)
    - Final draft screenplay by Stanley Kramer. (Box 47)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Continuities). (Box 48)
    - Production files (M.P.P.A. - Wardrobe). (Box 49)
    - Music cue sheets. (Box 50)
    - Complete music score. (Box 343, Box 344)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuities. (Box 50)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuities. (Box 51)
    - 925 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 52, Box 53)
      See also: Boxes 343, 344.
    - Press Book (Box 131)
  - The Pride and the Passion, 1957.
    - Piano score. (Box 12)
    - Music cue sheets and final dubbing. (Box 12)
    - Microgroove recording of Antheil's theme conducted by Ernest Gold. (Box 302)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Dialogue continuity). (Box 13)
    - Production files (El Escorial - Publicity). (Box 14)
    - Production files (Sinatra, Frank - Wardrobe). (Box 15)
    - Story outline. (Box 16)
    - Second draft, shooting script. (Box 16)
    - Final shooting script. (Box 16)
    - Final shooting script, Spanish. (Box 16)
    - Display photograph with Stanley Kramer. (Box 16)
    - Screen Directors' Guild plaque for nomination for Best Director. (Box 304)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 16)
      See also: Boxes 302, 303, 304, 337.
    - Small model cannon. (Box 304)
    - Second draft (2). (Box 250)
    - S. Kramer personal script. (Box 251)
    - Script in Spanish, Madrid Additional scenes shot in Hollywood., 1956 - (Box 251)
    - Final draft. Additional scenes shot in Hollywood. (Box 251)
    - The Pride and the Passion medal presented in Madrid, 1956. (Box 121)
      Scope and Content
      Parent Magazine Plaque.
    - Scrapbook of newsclippings. (Box 337)
    - Svenska Film Samfundet medallion, in case. (Box 304)
    - Music. (Box 302)
    - Production stills., (350) in 8 albums. (Box 303)
    - 15 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - 32 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - 34 Storyboards, 5 pages describing shots. (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - 10 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 10)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 9)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards, 4 pages describing shots. (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - 9 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Cary Grant).
    - Model cannon. (Box 304)
  - RPM
    - 2. Music. (Box 206)
    - 1. Album. Music from RPM. (Box 334)
    - 1. Revised pages. With notations., n.d. (Box 297)
    - 2. Script. First rough draft. pp. 1-46., Master sheets for photocopying. (Box 297)
    - 3. Script. Revised first draft:, October 3, 1969.; (orange cover). (Box 297)
    - 4. Script. Revisions from script no. 1 and 2. Replaced by revisions dated, October 16, 1969. October 17, 21 and 28. (Box 297)
    - 5. Script. Further revisions for `first draft' plus new pages up to end of picture., September 3, 1969. (Box 297)
    - 6. Script. Second rough draft. pp. 1-27. With notations. (Box 297)
    - 7. Script. pp. 1-25., August 27, 1969.; 3 copies. (Box 298)
    - 8. Script. Revisions for revised first draft:, October 13-28, 1969. (Box 298)
    - 9. Script. pp. 1-71., October 3, 1969. (Box 298)
    - Stills
      - 1. Key set stills--RPM. (Box 206)
      - 2. Eight cards with stills of location.
    - 10. Script. pp. 1-128. Revisions., October 1969. (Box 298)
    - 11. Script. pp. 72-105. With revisions., ca. October 1969. (Box 298)
    - Folders
      - 1. Segal, Erich (Plays, Incorporated writer)--Contract. (Box 195)
      - 2. Serling, Rod (Finger Lokes Production, Incorporated)--Contract. (Box 195)
      - 3. Set Continuity Lists. (Box 195)
      - 4. Suski, George (Campus Media, Incorporated), New York. (Box 195)
      - 5. Theatre Openings. (Box 195)
      - 6. Title Designers. (Box 195)
      - 7. University of the Pacific--Contract. (Box 195)
      - 8. Volkman, Ivan (Production Manager)--Correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 9. Wardrobe plot. (Box 195)
      - 10. Zagon, Schiff, Hirsch & Levine--Correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 11. Music - Barry DeVorzon (Songwriter), Perry Botkin, Jr. (Composer)--Contract. (Box 195)
      - 12. Music Cue Sheet. (Box 195)
      - 13. Music--Miscellaneous correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 14. Music--Soundtrack Album--Bell Records. (Box 195)
      - 15. Music--Songs--Melanie--Contract (Lyrics & Songs). (Box 195)
      - 16. Music--Song--Rudy Vallee. (Box 195)
      - 17. Publicity--Advertisements. (Box 195)
      - 18. Publicity--Beck, Myer Pages--Correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 19. Publicity--Glass, George--Correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 20. Publicity--Press Conference. (Box 195)
      - 21. Quinn, Anthony--Contract. (Box 195)
      - 22. Credits--Main Title & Advertising. (Box 195)
      - 23. Correspondence. (Box 195)
      - 24. Mailings (Permanent Record). (Box 195)
      - 25. Key Set Photos (Correspondence). (Box 195)
      - 26. Location Travel Arrangements. (Box 196)
      - 27. Photo Captions. (Box 196)
      - 28. Playdates. (Box 196)
      - 29. Premiere. (Box 196)
      - 30. Photo Coverage (Photographers). (Box 196)
      - 31. Photo Orders. (Box 196)
      - 32. Previews. (Box 196)
      - 33. Production Notes. (Box 196)
      - 34. Progress Reports. (Box 196)
      - 35. Release. (Box 196)
      - 36. Reviews (2). (Box 196)
      - 37. Promo - Radio / Television. (Box 196)
      - 38. Promotion--Miscellaneous. (Box 196)
      - 39. Promotion--Television Documentary. (Box 196)
      - 40. Bob Yeager Copy. (Box 196)
      - 41. Newspaper Clips. (Box 197)
      - 42. Magazine Clips (Trade Clips). (Box 197)
      - 42a. Trade clips. (Box 197)
      - 43. Release Date. (Box 197)
      - 44. Research (2). (Box 197)
      - 44a. Research (1). (Box 198)
      - 45. Screening. (Box 198)
      - 46. Crank Letters. (Box 198)
      - 47. Actors and Agents. (Box 198)
      - 48. Ann-Margaret--Contract. (Box 198)
      - 49. Actors--Day Player--ContractS. (Box 198)
      - 50. Actors--Weekly Contracts. (Box 198)
      - 51. Actors--Daily & Weekly--Stunt Men. (Box 198)
      - 52. Box Office Receipts. (Box 198)
      - 53. Brockman, Colin. (Box 198)
      - 54. Budget--Cost Reports--Pre-production & Production Costs. (Box 198)
      - 55. Budget--Estimated Detail. (Box 198)
      - 56. Cast & Crew Lists. (Box 198)
      - 57. Claim - Gary Rossiter vs. Columbia Pictures & S. Kramer. (Box 198)
      - 58. Clatworthy, Bob (Production Designer)--Contract. (Box 198)
      - 59. Columbia Pictures--Correspondence. (Box 198)
      - 60. Comments, Congratulations, Quotes, etc. (Box 198)
      - 61. Crew--Salary Agreements--Key Personnel. (Box 198)
      - 62. Editorial. (Box 199)
      - 63. Ferguson, Robert (Vice President of Advertising, Publicity & Expl.)--Correspondence. (Box 199)
      - 64. Gordon, Billy (Casting Department). (Box 199)
      - 65. Hotel lists. (Box 199)
      - 66. Hugo, Michael (cameraman)--Contract. (Box 199)
      - 67. Jaffe, Leo--Correspondence. (Box 199)
      - 68. Kramer, Stanley & Earl - Los Angeles County Health Department Notice. (Box 199)
      - 69. MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America). (Box 199)
      - 70. Synopsis. (Box 199)
      - 71. Book Novelization. (Box 199)
      - 72. Advertisements. (Box 199)
      - 73. Billing. (Box 199)
      - 74. Lockwood, Gary (Rossiter). (Box 199)
    - R. P. M. Featurette -- from Jack Atlas Columbia Pictures Hollywood Trailer Dept., 16mm color film (Box 131)
    - Scripts
      - 1. First draft:, September 2, 1969. (Box 199)
      - 2. First draft: With notations., September 2, 1969. (Box 199)
      - 3. First draft: pp. 1-87., September 2, 1969.
      - 4. First draft: pp. 1-93., September 2, 1969. (Box 199)
      - 5. Revised first draft:, October 3, 1969. (Box 200)
      - 6. Fifth draft: Screenplay by Rod Serling (2)., July 18, 1969. (Box 200)
      - 7. Script:, October 19. (Box 200)
      - 8. Final draft: Screenplay by Erich Segal. As shot (3)., November 3, 1969. (Box 200)
      - 9. Final draft: Screenplay by Erich Segal (2)., November 3, 1969. (Box 200)
      - 10. Final draft: As shot. Screenplay by Erich Segal (3)., November 3, 1969. (Box 201)
      - 11. Final draft: Close to as shot but not perfect. no. 152, 6, 153, 148, 158 (5)., November 3, 1969. (Box 201)
      - 12. Final draft: Screenplay by Erich Segal. no. 80, 138, 133, 2 (4)., November 3, 1969. (Box 202)
      - 13. Final draft: no. 73., November 3, 1969. (Box 202)
      - 14. Final draft: no. 70., November 20, 1969. (Box 202)
      - 15. Final draft. Screenplay by Erich Segal. Stanley Kramer's script. As shot. S. Kramer script editing., November 3, 1969. (Box 202)
      - 16. Final draft: Screenplay by Erich Segal. no. 157. With added lines by Gary Lockwood., November 3, 1969. (Box 202)
      - 17. Final draft: As shot. Screenplay by Erich Segal., November 3, 1969. (Box 203)
      - 18. Final draft: S. Kramer personal shooting script. With notations. Screenplay by Erich Segal., November 3, 1969. (Box 203)
      - 19. Script revisions., n.p., v.d.; Approximately 200 leaves, (Box 203)
      - 20. Script revisions., n.p., v.d.; Approximately 200 leaves, (Box 203)
      - 21. Discards. ,n.p., v.d.; Approximately 250 leaves, (Box 203)
      - 22. Script. pp. 3-93. (Box 204)
      - 23. Second/final draft: pp. [1] - 128. With notations., November 3, 1969. (Box 204)
      - 24. Final draft: As shot. S. Kramer script., November 3, 1969. (Box 204)
      - 25. Script. With notations., n.d. (Box 204)
      - 26. Script.revisions. With holograph notations., November 17, 1969. (Box 204)
      - 27. Combined continuities (4).
      - 28. Combined continuities (5). (Box 205)
      - 29. Continuities combined (2). (Box 205)
  - Runner Stumbles
    - Cinema Circulus Achievement Award presented to Stanley Kramer on the occasions of his 35th film, The Runner Stumbles. Division of Cinema/Television, University of Southern California, Laminated plaque., 9 November 1979.; 30.5 × 36.5 cm. (Box 362)
      Addition, September 1984.
    - 12 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - 19 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - 17 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Secret of Santa Vittoria
    - 16mm master footage. No sound. (Box 131)
    - Foreign Press Award for The Secret of Santa Vittoria, 1969. (Box 330)
    - Envelope containing photographs (8) and color transparencies (11) of Stanley Kramer. (Box 298)
    - Caricature by Sante Barelli, 25 × 30, oil.
    - Grazi Rotunno oil painting, 19 × 25, 1968.
    - Tavoluaris montage.
    - 3 rolls of sketches.
    - Adamo Vaticano oil painting, 13 × 16.
    - Scripts
      - 1. First rough draft (pp. 1-199). (Box 219)
      - 2. First draft (pp. 1-199) with S. Kramer notations. (Box 219)
      - 3. First draft: (6)., April 9, 1968 (Box 220)
      - 4. Script, (3)., April 18, 1968 (Box 221)
      - 5. Final, (1)., April 18, 1968 (Box 221)
      - 6. Exact Shooting Script (3). (Box 221)
      - 7. Exact final shooting script (before retyping). (Box 222)
      - 8. Exact final shooting script (after retyping). (Box 222)
      - 9. S. Kramer's shooting script. (Box 222)
      - 10. Continuity Combined (2). (Box 222)